Wildcat is a action, thriller, crime film directed by James Nunn.
An ex-black ops team reunite to pull off a desperate heist in order to
save the life of their leader’s eight-year-old daughter.
Ada, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Roman, played by Lewis Tan.
Mrs. Christina Vine, played by Alice Krige.
Frasier Mahoney, played by Charles Dance.
Edward, played by Rasmus Hardiker.
Cia, played by Mathilde Warnier.
Wildcat is a 2025 action thriller film directed by
James Nunn and written by Dominic Burns.
It stars Kate Beckinsale, Lewis Tan, Rasmus Hardiker, Alice Krige,
Bailey Patrick, Tom Bennett, Matt Willis, and Roxy Striar.
Wildcat was released in the United States on November 25, 2025.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.